Long, Richard H. Manuscript of Biography and Miscellany 5652
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Richard H. Long Manuscript of Biography and Miscellany
1900-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Long, Richard H.
5652
0.33 cubic feet
0.3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Includes a manuscript, newspaper clippings, and two convention proceedings of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America in Boston.
8230074
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Long was a successful shoe manufacturer and a Democratic politician, at one point a supporter of William Jennings Bryan.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Long, Richard H.
8230074
- Long was a successful shoe manufacturer and a Democratic politician, at one point a supporter of William Jennings Bryan. Includes a manuscript, newspaper clippings, and two convention proceedings of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America in Boston.. (Box 1)
  - Biography (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Recollections (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Obituaries, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Gubernatorial Election, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bankruptcy, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Mr. Watson, Come Here!", 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Photocopied article from American Heritage, Fall 1957.
  - News clippings, 1900-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Samuel Long, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Convention souvenir booklets. Photocopies